Inventory to the Annelise Graebner Anderson Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Annelise Graebner Anderson Papers
1968-1990
90032
Hoover Institution Archives
146 manuscript boxes, 3 phonorecords, 2 phonotapes, digital files. (61.2 linear feet)
Schedules, memoranda, correspondence, reports, notes, clippings, and sound recordings relating to the presidential campaign of Richard M. Nixon in 1968 and Ronald Reagan in 1980, and to preparations for the presidential administration of Ronald Reagan; and draft and final report, transcripts of meetings and hearings, correspondence, notes, press releases, and clippings, relating to activities of the President's Commission on Privatization in investigating and making recommendations concerning the desirability of transferring various functions and assets of the United States government to the private sector (conclusions published as Privatization: Toward More Effective Government: Report of the President's Commission on Privatization [Washington, 1988]).
Anderson, Annelise Graebner.
Access
Collection open for research. The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1990.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
An American economist, Annelise Graebner Anderson was a staff member for the Republican 1968 and 1980 presidential campaign committees, and a part of the 1980-1981 presidential transition team. During 1980, she was a senior policy adviser to the presidential campaign of Ronald Reagan, and as Associate Director of the Office of Presidential Personnel, worked on staffing the departments of Treasury, Transportation, and Commerce during the transition to the first Reagan administration.
From 1981 to 1983, Anderson was Associate Director for Economics and Government with the Office of Management and Budget (OMB), where she was responsible for the budgets of five cabinet departments (Treasury, Justice, Commerce, Transportation, and Housing and Urban Development) and over 40 other agencies. While at OMB, she participated actively in the development of the administration's policies with respect to housing and housing finance, deregulation of financial institutions, transportation, and immigration.
In 1983, she became n a Senior Research Fellow at the Hoover Institution. In 1987-1988, she served as a member, President's Commission on Privatization. She also advised the governments of Russia, and Romania, and the Republic of Georgia on economic reform and studied the transition process in Poland, the Czech Republic, and Mongolia.
Scope and Content of Collection
Schedules, memoranda, correspondence, reports, transcripts of meetings and hearings, notes, briefing papers, budget data, press releases, clippings, and sound recordings relating to the presidential campaigns of Richard M. Nixon in 1968 and Ronald Reagan in 1980; preparation for the Reagan presidential administration; preparation of budgets during the Reagan presidential administration; domestic policy issues and economic conditions during the Reagan presidential administration; and activities of the President's Commission on Privatization in investigating and making recommendations concerning the desirability of transferring various functions and assets of the United States government to the private sector.
Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; Reagan, Ronald.; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); United States. Office of Management and Budget.; United States. President's Commission on Privatization.; Budget--United States.; Economists.; Government ownership--United States.; Government productivity--United States.; Laissez-faire.; Presidents--United States--Election--1968.; Presidents--United States--Election--1980.; Privatization--United States.; United States--Economic conditions--1981-2001.; United States--Economic policy--1981-1993.; United States--Politics and government--1981-1989.
- President’s Commission on Privatization file, 1987-1988 (Box 1-14)
  - Note to commissioners/Report of the President’s commission on Privatization (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Pre-typeset copies of the Introduction, low-income Housing, Housing Finance, and Contracting out chapters (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Naval Petroleum Reserves/Privatization and Economic Public Policy/Medicare, A.I.D., and Urban Mass Transit (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Interim recommendations/Low-income Housing/Housing Finance/Issues and Options (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Military Commissaries/Contractual Operations of Prisons and Jails/Education and Democracy/Meeting-December 21, 1987 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Public Hearings-December 22, 1987 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Public Hearing on Education-December 21, 1987 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Medicare Privatization (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Privatization and the Agency for International Development (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Business Meeting, December 1, 1987 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Business Meeting, February 22, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Public Hearing on Air Traffic Control and other functions of the Federal Aviation Administration-December 1, 1987 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Hearing on Air Traffic Control System-December 2, 1987 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Issues and options paper on loan portfolio privatization issues (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Business Meeting-January 7, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Hearing on contracting out-January 7, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Hearing on contracting out-January 8, 1988 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Briefing Papers (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - Articles on educational issues (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Briefing papers on contracting Prison Management and Mass Transit (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Air Traffic Control and other FAA Functions/Educational Choice/Privatization of the Naval Petroleum reserves/Postal monopoly/Amtrak (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Issues and options in Postal Service Privatization/Business meeting-December 1, 1987/Amtrak/Contracting out briefing paper (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - Business meeting-February 5, 1988 (Box-folder 3: 7)
  - Business meeting-January 28, 1988/Public Hearing on Asset sales-January 28, 1988 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Public Hearing on Asset sales-January 29, 1988 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Privatization on postal service (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - Issues on postal services/Medicare/International Development/Conrail/Amtrak (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Mass transit/Sales of capital assets briefing paper/Naval petroleum reserves (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Naval Petroleum Reserve/Lessons from British success stories/Amtrak/Postal Service – 1988 (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - 1988 Legislative and administrative message/Executive order September 3, 1987/US-UK relations briefing paper (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - NY Times clippings 1987/Proposed National Aviation Authority/National Academy of Public Administration/Aviation Programs (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Survey of issue priorities/Federal Housing Finance Programs/NY Times clippings/Privatization 1987/Federal Aviation Administration Programs – November 20, 1987 (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - National Air Transportation System (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - National Air Transportation System/Privatization on Amtrak/Misc. notes (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Special Report/Amtrak passengers/Privatization in developing countries/Federal Asset sales-January 29, 1988/Medicare privatization (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Business meeting-November 9, 1987/Military commissaries/Education and democracy/Contractual operations of prisons and jails/Misc. notes (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Final summary and recommendations of the town meeting on privatization – January 19, 1988 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Hearing on “Loan Portfolio Divestiture” – November 10, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Business Meeting – September 30, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - The Privatization Review/The Marketing Plan of Naval Petroleum reserves 1 and 3/Privatizing the welfare state (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - An Introduction to CMO’s/Draft Interim Report/The Privatization Council (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Public Hearings on Housing Issues/Management and Budget/Statement of Barry Anderson (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Third and Fourth Subject Segments/Issues and options paper on loan portfolio privatization issues/Privatization in housing (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Historical Developments of FNMA/Revolution in mortgage finance/CSE Reports/Clippings and notes (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - Biotherapeutics/Selling the Federal Loan Portfolio/Hearings on Air Traffic Control/Brookings Dialogues (Box-folder 7: 6)
  - Public Hearings on Housing Issues- October 21, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 1-3)
  - Meeting – October 20, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 4)
  - Public Hearing – October 20, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 5)
  - Briefing and Orientation meeting – September 18, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 6)
  - Contracting/Privatization and the Agency for International Development/Federal Loan Programs (CH 4)/Traffic Control (CH 5)/Educational Choice (CH 6) (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - Briefing and orientation meeting – September 18, 1987/Business meeting – September 30, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - Meeting – October 20, 1987/Public Hearing – October 20, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 2)
  - Public Hearings on Housing Issues – October 21, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 3)
  - Business meeting – November 9, 1987/Public Hearing on “Loan Portfolio Divestiture” – November 9, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 4)
  - Public Hearing on Loan Portfolio Divestiture – November 10, 1987/Business meeting – December 1, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - Public Hearing on Air Traffic Control and other functions of the federal Aviation Administration – December 1, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 6)
  - Public Hearing on Air Traffic Control System – December 2, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Business meeting – December 21, 1987/Public Hearing on Education – December 21, 1987 (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - Public Hearing – December 22, 1987 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Public Hearing on Contracting Out – January 7, 1988/Business meeting – January 7, 1988 (Box-folder 10: 3)
  - Public Hearing on Contracting Out – January 8, 1988/Business meeting – January 28, 1988 (Box-folder 10: 4)
  - Public Hearing on Asset sales – January 28, 1988 (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - Public Hearing on Asset sales – January 29, 1988 (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - Business meeting – February 5, 1988 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Business meeting – February 22, 1988/Business meeting agenda – October 20, 1987 (Box-folder 11: 2)
  - Business meeting – October 20, 1987 (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Housing Privatization related materials provided to the commission – September 30, 1987 (Box-folder 11: 4-5)
  - Business meeting agenda – November 9, 1987 (Box-folder 12: 1-2)
  - Business meeting agenda – December 1-2, 1987 (Box-folder 12: 3-5)
  - Business meeting agenda – December 21-22, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 1-2)
  - Business meeting agenda – January 7, 1988 (Box-folder 13: 3-5)
  - Business meeting agenda – January 28, 1988 (Box-folder 13: 6)
  - Business meeting agenda – January 28, 1988 (Box-folder 14: 1-2)
  - Business meeting agenda – February 5-6, 1988 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Business meeting agenda – February 22, 1988 (Box-folder 14: 4-5)
- Richard Nixon/Spiro Agnew presidential/vice presidential campaign, 1968 (Box 15-17)
  - Idea memos (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Press/Staff schedule – 1968 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Notes on seabed and oceanography (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - Staff memos (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Oceanography – correspondence (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Research Organization (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Notes/Note cards (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - Personal (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Economy (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Delegates (Box-folder 16: 2-3)
  - Summary of positions/notes (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Tax sharing/Excerpts from policy statements (Box-folder 16: 5)
  - Research work (Box-folder 16: 6)
  - Maritime Affairs (Box-folder 16: 7)
  - Travel Tax (Box-folder 16: 8)
  - Memos on the Republican Party Platform (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Oceanography drafts (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - RPN (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Miscellaneous work done (Box-folder 17: 4-5)
  - Candidate lists according to position (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Election (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Education Statement Requests/Miscellaneous (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Alaska (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Youth (Box-folder 17: 11)
- Ronald Reagan presidential campaign, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Reagan-Bush Briefing Book for Bush Plane (Box-folder 18: 1-2)
  - Report of Receipts and Expenditures (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Itemized receipts, contributions, ticket purchases, loans, rebates, and transfers for line numbers 15, 16, 17 and/CP 18 (Box-folder 18: 4)
  - Clippings/Notes (Box-folder 18: 5-7)
- Ronald Reagan/George Bush presidential/vice presidential campaign, 1980 (Box 19-25)
  - Later (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Research (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Policy (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - Office – DO (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Legislative update (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Political//AA (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Memorandums/Notes/Clippings (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Drafts/Notes (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Campaign song/Schedules/Clippings/Memorandums/Notes (Box-folder 19: 9)
  - Education (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - Abscam (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - Poland (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Energy (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Billy (Box-folder 19: 14)
  - China (Box-folder 19: 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - CIA Agent Disclosure (For Bush) (Box-folder 19: 17)
  - The economy (Box-folder 19: 18)
  - Jerusalem (Box-folder 19: 19)
  - Stealth (Box-folder 19: 20)
  - Ciuiletti background (Box-folder 19: 21)
  - Demos/Mondale (Box-folder 19: 22)
  - Economy – data (Box-folder 19: 23)
  - Shrimp industry (Box-folder 19: 24)
  - National Shrimp Congress Briefing Kit/The Plight of the U.S. Shrimp Industry – September 17, 1980 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - 1980 Presidential Debates press kit (Box-folder 20: 2)
  - Women (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Misuse in office (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Economy – Attacks on U.S. (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Low road/Mondale (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Salt/Muskie (Box-folder 20: 7)
  - NP (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Salt II (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - Carter econ program (Box-folder 20: 10)
  - Steel (Box-folder 20: 11)
  - Waste/Fraud (Box-folder 20: 12)
  - Demo platform – cost (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Notes/Clippings (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - AA Carter (Box-folder 20: 15)
  - Polls (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Foreign/Defense (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - The STEALTH controversy/U.S./Soviet Military Balance/Notes (Box-folder 21: 2)
  - Miscellaneous issues (Box-folder 21: 3-4)
  - Current (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - Tour (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Current information (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Bush memos/Assignments (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Bush statements (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Requests made (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Economy (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Notes/OMB study/Memorandums (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Early briefings (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - Morning meeting (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - Baltimore Debate/Notes (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Guest and staff instructions/Schedules (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Schedules (Box-folder 22: 7-10)
  - Debates – Briefing book (Box-folder 23: 1-2)
  - News releases (Box-folder 23: 4-7)
  - Articles/Memorandums (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - State Reagan Bush Headquarters, temporary offices, and officers/Staff Directory (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - Policy Coordination (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - News releases/RR speaks out on the issues (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - News releases (Box-folder 24: 2-4)
  - Ohio/Pennsylvania/Ohio/Mississippi/Tennessee/Florida/South Carolina Briefings /Memorandums (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - State briefings/Material on timber (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - State briefings/Daily News Digest/Campaign notes (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Memorandums (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Clippings/Memorandums (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Draft of Teamsters Speech/Office of Policy Coordination (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - RR Draft (Box-folder 25: 3-4)
  - Policy papers/Energy speech drafts (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - Energy Policy Paper/Schedules (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Schedules (Box-folder 25: 7-8)
- Ronald Reagan presidential transition team, 1980-1981 (Box 26-27)
  - Fiscal and Monetary Policy Task Force (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Social Issues/Task Force on Defense and Foreign Policy (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Government Regulation and the Free Enterprise System Task Force (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Social Issues/Housing and transportation task force/Agriculture task force/General energy policy (Box-folder 26: 12)
  - General Energy Policy/The Carter Record in Foreign Policy and National Security/Council of Economic advisors (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - Congress of the United States-Joint economic committee (Box-folder 26: 14)
  - Treasury records (Box-folder 26: 15)
  - Treasury-GEN (Box-folder 26: 16)
  - Memos-General (Box-folder 26: 17)
  - Press Releases (Box-folder 26: 18)
  - Phone numbers/presidential personnel roster/Office of the president-elect/treasury department (Box-folder 26: 19)
  - Contact Sheets (Box-folder 26: 20)
  - Department of the Treasury/Office of the president-elect (Box-folder 26: 21)
  - Transportation records/commerce records (Box-folder 26: 22)
  - Special Trade Representative/small business administration (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Basic Documents (Box-folder 27: 2)
  - National Journal/Memorandum (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - Treasury Recruiters (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - Wed./personal (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - 1980 Transition/Personnel (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Forecasts (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Misc./Old notes (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Recs/recruiting/pre-inaugural Budget (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - OMB/phone numbers/task forces (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Deputy Secretary/Policy and Supporting Positions (Box-folder 27: 11)
- Office of Management and Budget, 1981-1983 (Box 28-139)
  - Memorandums (Box-folder 28: 1-4)
  - Misc./Debt Ceiling (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - Memorandums (Box-folder 28: 6-7)
  - Coast Guard Budget- 83/84 (Box-folder 29: 8)
  - Memorandums (Box-folder 29: 9-11)
  - Economic report/mid-session review of the 1983 budget (Box-folder 29: 12)
  - 1981/82 (Box-folder 29: 13)
  - Sensitive Issues (Box-folder 29: 14)
  - Memorandums,1982 (Box-folder 29: 15)
  - Memorandums/A95 Policies (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - Grant-in-aid outlay estimates/memorandums/monthly data for CPI, PPI, unemployment rate (Box-folder 30: 2)
  - Memorandums/Clippings (Box-folder 30: 3-4)
  - Stockman briefing papers-NYC (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - Memorandums/Notes (Box-folder 31: 1-3)
  - Memorandums/status of administration-sponsored legislation/housing subsidy proposals/budget authority (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - FFB (Box-folder 31: 5)
  - Federal Civilian Retiree COLA/Disposal of Excess and Surplus Federal Property/Memorandums/ (Box-folder 31: 6)
  - Military/Civilian Retirement (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - NHTSA/NCUA (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - National Consumer Cooperative Bank (NCCB (Box-folder 32: 1-2)
  - Nuclear Equipment Working Group (NEWG) (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Cabinet Council on Commerce and Trade (CCCT) (Box-folder 32: 4)
  - The National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee (LAOOC) (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - Management Meeting Agenda (Box-folder 32: 7)
  - Policy Meeting Agenda (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - Legislative Affairs Meeting Agenda (Box-folder 32: 9)
  - Senior Staff Meeting (Box-folder 32: 10)
  - OMB Staff Meeting (Box-folder 32: 11)
  - Marad (Box-folder 32: 12-13)
  - Justice Issues (Box-folder 33: 1-2)
  - SBA-82 Appeal/83-84 Budget (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - Spring Review (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - Misc. (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - User Charge Policy (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Maritime Policy (Box-folder 33: 7-8)
  - AA Methods for FFB interest payments to treasury (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs (Box-folder 33: 10)
  - Minority Business (Box-folder 33: 11)
  - Mid-session review (Box-folder 33: 12)
  - Mid term planning (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - MSPB (Box-folder 33: 14)
  - Econ Assumptions (Box-folder 33: 15)
  - HUD (Box-folder 33: 16)
  - Commerce (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - 1983 Spring Planning Review DOT (Box-folder 34: 2-3)
  - misc. subject files (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - U.S. Metric Board (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - MGT (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Sealift and Shipbuilding (Box-folder 34: 7)
  - Title XI Loan Guarantees (Box-folder 34: 8)
  - Legislative Problems (Box-folder 34: 9)
  - Transportation (Box-folder 34: 10)
  - LANDSAT (Box-folder 34: 11)
  - 1983 PAD Review DOT (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - DOC/SBA FY 1983 Spring Preview (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - 1983 Budget DOT (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - 83 Budget Wrap-up (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box-folder 35: 5-6)
  - Analysis of Pay Costs Increases (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - HUD BRB Appeal Session (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - First Budget Resolution FY 83 (Box-folder 36: 2-4)
  - 1983 Spring Review OIRA (Box-folder 36: 5)
  - Transmittal Letters (Box-folder 36: 6)
  - CBO estimates/Spending proposals/Latta function summary/Draft resolution/HBC Testimony (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - CBO Pricing/Budget Discussion notebooks and materials/Bipartisan recovery budget (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - Future Budget Outlook: Resources, Requirements, and Choices (Box-folder 37: 3)
  - Major Themes and Additional Budget Details (Box-folder 37: 4-5)
  - HUD 1983 Director’s Review (Box-folder 38: 1-2)
  - Appropriations (Box-folder 38: 3)
  - Appropriations/Bipartisan Recovery Budget/Domenici Budget (Box-folder 38: 4)
  - Director’s Briefing Book Volume II (Box-folder 38: 5-7)
  - Director’s Briefing Book Volume III (Box-folder 38: 8)
  - Director’s Briefing Book Volume III (Box-folder 39: 1-2)
  - 1983 Continuing Resolution (Box-folder 39: 3)
  - 1981 Outlay Reductions (Box-folder 39: 4)
  - Reconciliation Issues (Box-folder 39: 5)
  - Side-By-Side – Arranged by House Committee Followed by Block Grants (Box-folder 39: 6-7)
  - Capital budgeting materials (Box-folder 39: 8)
  - Capital budgeting materials (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - Treasury (Box-folder 40: 2-3)
  - Budget Review (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - Transcript from American Debate/Capital budget (Box-folder 40: 5)
  - State and Local Fiscal Condition Fall 1982 (Box-folder 40: 6)
  - Capital budgeting briefing book – 6/6/82 (Box-folder 40: 7)
  - Background material for testimony before the subcommittee on economic development of the house committee on public works – March, 11, 1981 (Box-folder 41: 1-2)
  - Jobs II (Box-folder 41: 3)
  - EDA (Box-folder 41: 4-5)
  - Public Works (Box-folder 41: 6)
  - 1984 Small Agency Review-Economics + Government (Box-folder 42: 1-5)
  - 1984 Budget- Director’s Review – Justice, Treasury, and Personnel (Box-folder 42: 6-7)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box-folder 42: 8)
  - General Services Administration (Box-folder 42: 9)
  - Detailed rack-up of possible federal construction and repairs funding acceleration (Box-folder 42: 10)
  - Proposal for an Emergency Food Assistance Program (Box-folder 42: 11)
  - Highway Program (Box-folder 42: 12)
  - Federal Aviation Administration Airport Improvement Grants (Box-folder 42: 13)
  - Possible Jobs and Assistance Package (Box-folder 42: 14)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box-folder 42: 15)
  - BRB Appeals Session – December 14, 1982 – HUD/Veterans Administration (Box-folder 43: 1)
  - BRB Appeals Session – December 13, 1982 – Department of labor/transportation/treasury (Box-folder 43: 2)
  - INS/Customs (Box-folder 43: 3)